thetones360.com 2010-10-09

# TheTones360 Privacy Notice

  | 

## Personal Information

  * **Non-Account Activity.** You can listen ringtones on TheTones360 without having a TheTones360 Account. You can also contact us about a particular ringtones without having a TheTones360 Account.
  * **Account-Related Activity.** Certain other activities on TheTones360-like uploading music, posting comments, flagging ringtones, or listen restricted ringtones-require you to have a TheTones360 Account. We ask for some personal information when you create a TheTones360 Account, including your email address and a password, which is used to protect your account from unauthorized access.
  * **Usage Information.** We may record information about your usage, such as when you use TheTones360, the channels, groups, and favorites you subscribe to, the contacts you communicate with, the ringtones you listen, and the frequency and size of data transfers, as well as information you display or click on in TheTones360 (including UI elements, settings, and other information). If you are logged in, we may associate that information with your account. We may use clear GIFs (a.k.a. "Web Beacons") in HTML-based emails sent to our users to track which emails are opened by recipients.
  * **Content Uploaded to Site.** Any personal information or music content that you voluntarily disclose online (on discussion boards, in messages and chat areas, within your playback or profile pages, etc.) becomes publicly available and can be collected and used by others.

## Uses

  * If you submit personally identifiable information to us through the TheTones360 Site, we use your personal information to operate, maintain, and provide to you the general and personalized features and functionality of the TheTones360 Site, and to process any flagging activity or correspondence you send to us.
  * Your account name (not your email address) is displayed to other Users when you upload ringtones or send messages through the TheTones360 Site and other Users can contact you through messages and comments. Any ringtones that you submit to the TheTones360 Site may be redistributed through the internet and other media channels, and may be viewed by the general public. 
  * We do not use your email address or other personally identifiable information to send commercial or marketing messages without your consent or except as part of a specific program or feature for which you will have the ability to opt-in or opt-out. We may, however, use your email address without further consent for non-marketing or administrative purposes (such as notifying you of major TheTones360 Site changes or for customer service purposes).
  * We use both your personally identifiable information and certain non-personally-identifiable information (such as anonymous user usage data, cookies, IP addresses, browser type, clickstream data, etc.) to improve the quality and design of the TheTones360 Site and to create new features, promotions, functionality, and services by storing, tracking, analyzing, and processing user preferences and trends, as well as user activity and communications.
  * We use cookies, clear gifs, and log file information to: (a) store information so that you will not have to re-enter it during your visit or the next time you visit the TheTones360 Site; (b) provide custom, personalized content and information; (c) monitor the effectiveness of our marketing campaigns; (d) monitor aggregate metrics such as total number of visitors, pages viewed, etc.; and (e) track your entries, submissions, and status in promotions, sweepstakes, and contests. 
  * We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our website. These companies may use information (not including your name, address, email address, or telephone number) about your visits to this and other websites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, [click here](http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html).

## Information That is Publicly Available

  * When you create an account on the site, some information about your account and your account activity will be provided to other Users of the site. This may include the date you opened your account, the date you last logged into your account, your age (if you choose to make it public), the country and the number of ringtones you have download.
  * Your account name (not your email address) is displayed to other Users when you engage in certain activity on the site, such as you upload content or send messages through the TheTones360 Site. Other Users can contact you through messages and comments.
  * You may also choose to add personal information that will visible to other Users on your channel page (which is the public facing page for your account on the site). This may include a profile picture, you name, gender, relationship status, or other details.
  * If you choose to add certain features to your channel page, then these features and your activity associated with these features will be displayed to other Users and may be aggregated and shared with your confirmed friends or other Users. Such shared activity may include what ringtone you favorite, what ringtone you rated and what ringtones you have uploaded.
  * Any ringtones that you submit to the TheTones360 Site may be redistributed through the internet and other media channels, and may be viewed by the general public. 

## Your Choices

  * You may, of course, decline to submit personally identifiable information through the TheTones360 Site, in which case you can still listen ringtones and explore the TheTones360 Site, but TheTones360 may not be able to provide certain services to you. Some advanced TheTones360 features may, for authentication purposes, require you to sign up for other TheTones360 services. The privacy notices of those services govern the use of your personal information associated with them.
  * You may update or correct your personal profile information and email preferences at any time by visiting your account profile page.
  * You may clear your viewing history at any time through the "Viewing History" feature.
  * You may control the information that is available to other Users and your confirmed friends at any time by editing your account and the features that are included on your channel page.

## Third-party Advertisers, Links to Other Sites

TheTones360 allows other companies, called third-party ad servers or ad networks, to serve advertisements within the TheTones360 Sites. These third-party ad servers or ad networks use technology to send, directly to your browser, the advertisements and links that appear on the TheTones360 Site. They automatically receive your IP address when this happens. They may also use other technologies (such as cookies, JavaScript, or Web Beacons) to measure the effectiveness of their advertisements and to personalize the advertising content you see.

TheTones360 does not provide any personally identifiable information to these third-party ad servers or ad networks without your consent or except as part of a specific program or feature for which you will have the ability to opt-in or opt-out. However, please note that if an advertiser asks TheTones360 to show an advertisement to a certain audience (for example, men ages 18-34) or audience segment (for example, men ages 18-24 who have listen certain channels of content) and you respond to that advertisement, the advertiser or ad-server may conclude that you fit the description of the audience they are trying to reach. The advertiser may also use information regarding your use of the TheTones360 Site, such as the number of times you viewed an ad (but not any personally identifiable information), to determine which ads to deliver to you.

|
